(Ito Junji)
(I'll get you a meeting with him.)
(Thus began...)
(Kian84's journey to meet his role model.)
(He's been studying Japanese for this day.)
(He even prepared boxed meals with a lot of love.)
(Pressing)
(Satisfied)
(And...)
(Kian84 prepared...)
(To me, Ito Junji...)
(reminds me of space...)
(and a black hole.)
(His sincere admiration toward his role model)
(At last, he's about to meet...)
(his role model.)
(The most nerve-racking moment)
(Utterly nervous)
(He finally enters the meeting place.)
(He gulps down water as he's nervous.)
(Getting nervous too)
- I'm getting nervous for him. - Same here.
(I'm getting nervous for him.)
You don't look confident at all.
Why did I ask to meet him? That was unnecessary.
I'm getting dizzy. This is bad.
You have to help me. When I'm struggling,
- please help me a lot. - Of course.
I'll try to read the vibe first.
(Exhaling)
Imagine going there by yourself without Kangnam.
Gosh, I couldn't have survived.
(Feeling dizzy)
I started to study Japanese...
since the last time I met you.
You improved, though.
- Has it been six months? - Yes.
I've been studying for six months. He's here.
I've been studying for six months.
(Is that a knock on the door?)
- He's here. - He's here.
(Their guest arrives even before they had a chance to relax.)
- Sir. It's nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
(Nice to meet you.)
You became a boy again.
Sir.
- My goodness. It's really him. - Yes.
(It's really Ito Junji.)
My gosh.
- I'm getting emotional for him. - Me too.
Go ahead and say hello to him.
(Rushing over)
(A meeting with his role model he dreamed of for a long time)
- My gosh. - Nice to meet you.
This is so surreal.
- It's so surreal. - Yes.
- Here? - You can sit on that side.
Kangnam is a good host.
(Kangnam naturally shows him to his seat.)
(Bowing again)
(Now that his role model is in front of him, his head goes blank.)
Once I met him in person,
it was just a jaw-dropping moment.
I couldn't believe he was right in front of me.
It felt like...
(Like a storm, stirring in his heart)
I was meeting someone who felt almost unreal.
That was such a surreal moment.
My gosh. I was just over the moon.
You must have been dazed.
Well, growing up in Korea,
there used to be a book rental shop around my house.
And I borrowed his manga books as a kid.
The fact that I was meeting him...
Meeting him couldn't have been a big deal...
if he had made many public appearances.
- Right. He doesn't. - But he doesn't do that.
- I'm grateful to Kangnam again. - Right.
(Nervous)
So...
(Smiling)
meeting you like this...
feels like a dream.
- Thank you. - It was nice.
(He carefully delivers the introduction he practiced.)
I grew up reading your manga.
I dreamed of becoming a cartoonist...
I see.
(Whispering)
after reading your manga.
(Relieved)
It's an honor.
Do you want to introduce yourself first?
- Introduce myself? - You should start with that.
- I should do that. - Yes.
- I am... - Yes.
So...
- I've been a cartoonist... - Yes.
in Korea...
for 10 minutes. No, 10 years.
"For ten minutes."
"I've been drawing cartoons in Korea for ten minutes."
My brain was working at full capacity. I'm serious.
I watched a video about your solo exhibit...
on YouTube.
He watched you on YouTube.
(He's seen my artworks?)
I felt so shy when he said he had seen my work.
He watched a video about your solo exhibit?
He watched a video of our show.
That's right. It's also on YouTube.
- I thought it was cute. - You think he's cute?
- I meant, his art was cute. - His art?
Thank you.
(Not knowing what to do with himself)
There's something I'd like to tell you.
- It was 1994. - Yes.
In front of my house,
there was an old bookstore.
That was where I read...
your manga for the first...
- "Time." - time.
Your manga...
had a big influence on my.
It's "on me."
(He makes a series of mistakes as he's nervous.)
I'm sorry. I studied Japanese only for a short time.
- You're very good. - He said you were good.
It's only been six months he began studying.
- But he already speaks so well. - He studied hard.
So to me...
(He only focuses on what to say next.)
you are...
like a white hole?
- A black hole? - Yes, a black hole.
- What are you trying to say? - A black hole...
That's what you are to me. My gosh.
I see. To him,
you're like a black hole in space that draws people in.
(Grateful)
- So I prepared a present. - Okay.
- The painting? - You'll start with the painting?
I bet he's going to love it.
(The night before, he thought about his cosmic-like role model.)
Here's the present.
(Kian84 gives him the portrait he painted with great care.)
You did a superb job with it.
- How long did it take? - How long did it take?
Three hours?
- Three hours? - Three hours.
- Excellent. You did a great job. - That's...
That's you from your younger days.
(Feeling proud)
This was already 20 years ago.
- It was 20 years ago. - It was 20 years ago?
I wore the glasses then.
The glasses were from 20 years ago.
He remembers the glasses.
You must've been so happy.
You are still a youngster.
"A youngster?"
- "You still look young." - You still look young.
No.
(Laughing)
I turned 63 years old this year.
He's 63 years old.
(My role model is already that old?)
I'm impressed by how well you captured me in the painting.
You did a great job. He's impressed.
His solo exhibit had excellent paintings of cute faces.
His realistic paintings are great too.
- The thing is, - Right.
hearing compliments...
from the artist I really admired...
- felt amazing. - Of course.
- It's touching. - Yes.
(As they talk about art, he thinks of a question.)
Out of all your characters,
- Souichi is my favorite one. - Really?
(Souichi always has nails in his mouth...)
(because he has an iron deficiency.)
(He's a bit twisted.)
(He reminds me of myself when I was young.)
In my opinion,
(Hesitant)
you might have had similarities to Souichi...
when you were young.
(Perhaps, you were similar to Souichi.)
- That's right. - He said you were right.
- Really? - He was.
You seem to understand him well.
- Really? - You were right.
Souichi was based on what I was like as a kid.
But I wasn't that rebellious.
He wasn't that rebellious, though.
(I see.)
Then,
did you perhaps have...
nails in your mouth?
No, I didn't do that.
(Chuckling)
"Did he have nails in his mouth?"
I was wondering if it was based on his childhood.
I have low blood pressure.
I wondered if it had to do with iron deficiency.
At first, I thought about putting iron marbles in his mouth.
So he could spit them out as weapons.
But I thought nails in his mouth...
would be more interesting.
Low blood pressure...
- He didn't have... - He needed more iron.
- I've never told anyone about it. - He's never...
told anyone about it.
Then where did you get your inspiration for "Uzumaki?"
(He keeps asking questions like a kid who just learned to talk.)
(Listening intently)
Are Yon and Mu still alive?
Then is it their baby?
The baby between Yon and Mu?
You even asked about his cats?
- You wanted to ask him everything. - Yes.
It's not easy to meet him.
- He said everything on his mind. - Yes.
He has so many questions for you. I'm serious.
I guess you had that big of an influence on him.
(Grateful)
He was also number one webtoonist in Korea.
I can't read Korean, so I don't know the plot.
But I've seen his drawings.
He said he read your webtoon.
What?
(You even read my webtoon?)
He didn't get the plot,
- but he saw your drawings. - How did he come across it?
He's seen it.
I'm quite embarrassed.
My drawings were awful.
I'm so embarrassed.
What? No way.
- That's an artistic painting. - Look how good he is.
That's an artistic painting.
(Feeling small in front of his idol)
Should I say it was more realistic?
- His drawings were fun to look at. - He said they were fun to look at.
"Am I dreaming?"
It did feel like I was dreaming.
(It left an impression on me.)
- Sir. - Yes.
Would you like...
to eat?
Would you like to eat?
I'm a bit hungry.
He's a bit hungry. He hasn't eaten yet.
I actually cooked...
this morning.
- Really? - He cooked.
(He packed boxed meals for his idol this morning.)
(His best dish, kimchi fried rice)
(As someone who has had his fried rice...)
Gosh, I'm worried about this.
I was more nervous giving him the boxed meal than the painting.
If you don't mind, would you like to eat with us?
- Sure. - Would you like to?
It's cold. I wonder if he will mind.
It looks good. I'm sure it tastes fine.
I was worried because it got cold.
He should have eaten it when it was hot.
(Looking around)
(What's wrong?)
Hey, I forgot chopsticks.
(Things are getting worse.)
- I forgot chopsticks. - I'll go and get them.
- No. - No, I'll go and get them.
- You will? - I should go.
Where will you get them?
- I... Really? - No, I'll go.
- Excuse me. - Sure.
He's not usually like that. But he's nervous.
(Chuckling)
I could feel my face getting hot.
- Your face is red. - Yes, it got red.
You're like a guy who's never been on a blind date.
(There will be chopsticks, right?)
Hey, Kangnam.
Does warabasi mean chopsticks?
- It's waribasi. - Waribasi?
(I see. He didn't bring chopsticks.)
(Trying to speak for Kian84 for leaving to find chopsticks)
After we became friends, he only talked about you.
Really?
- Did you get them? - Yes.
- What a relief. - He got them.
This is yours. And this one is his.
- I made this. - Why...
Why did you make this face?
Thank you.
Do you make good fried rice?
Fried rice? Gosh, one of the eyes got separated.
(The eyes get separated.)
- My gosh, the eyes. - No!
- No! - My gosh.
- That must hurt. - No!
That has the same vibe as his manga.
- Right. The boxed meal lost an eye. - Yes.
(The grotesque unboxing of the boxed meal)
- One of the eyes got separated. - What?
(He picks up the separated eye.)
(Putting it back)
He's so thoughtful.
(Wait. Is that...)
- Is that a face? - It's a face.
(Ta-da)
I tried to mimic your drawing style.
Thank you for the meal.
Dig in, sir.
(I hope he likes the food.)
I was super worried about the food.
(Glancing)
(He scoops up the food and puts it in his mouth.)
(Stir-Fry84 shared...)
(his kimchi fried rice on the field day.)
(The flavor of the kimchi fried rice made everyone...)
(who bravely tried the food go speechless.)
(Will he be able to speak after trying the food?)
(Heart pounding)
(Please...)
- It's tasty. - It is?
(It's tasty.)
- It is? - Yes.
It's tasty.
(Mumbling)
(He has a bite of the food at ease after getting his feedback.)
- Kian84. This is good. - Yes?
It's a bit chilly.
- Chilly? You mean, "cold." - Cold?
- So the food is cold. - It's okay.
- It's still very tasty. - My gosh.
He said it was tasty even cold.
He's so sweet.
It's fried rice.
- "Fried rice." - This is fried rice.
- It's kimchi fried rice. - So...
it's kimchi fried rice.
- It's kimchi. - Yes, it's kimchi fried rice.
Kimchi doesn't taste good unless it's from Korea.
He said Korean kimchi was tasty.
Where did you get this kimchi?
I got it here.
A convenience store...
- Don't tell him that. - Okay.
"Don't tell him."
- We don't have to correct it. - Right.
- I bet he had no idea. - Exactly.
He thought the kimchi was from Korea.
Let's keep him in the dark.
(Glancing)
(Kian84 checks his reaction.)
(Kian84 has another bite since he likes to enjoy it.)
(A big bite)
- Were you hungry? - Well,
after asking him all the questions I prepared,
my head went blank.
- Ask him questions while you eat. - What?
In Japan, people talk during meals.
- Really? - Yes.
(Feel free to talk.)
(In that case...)
Is the food...
- tasty? - It's tasty.
- You already asked that. - It's tasty.
I'm nervous.
It's tasty.
I have you to thank for this boxed meal.
- Really? - I tested it on you.
(A good friend who agreed to be a test subject)
- Can you cook it again? - Thank you.
- I want to try the tasty version. - Okay.
- I want the tasty version. - Okay. I'll cook it again.
He was able to cook delicious fried rice...
- Yes. - because he failed previously.
What a relief.
(Kian84 asks a question spontaneously...)
(after making sure he likes the food.)
What are you into these days?
I would get invited to attend events abroad.
Since I can't speak English,
it's a bit uncomfortable.
So I've been studying English every day for five minutes.
I'm studying with Duolingo.
- Duolingo? - Yes.
That app is also famous in Korea.
I've been doing it more than 1,000 days consecutively.
- That's amazing. - He's been very diligent.
Then can you communicate when a foreigner talks to you?
- I can't. - No?
I'm at that age where I easily forget new information.
- It's admirable that he's still... - That's amazing.
- studying even at his age. - Exactly.
That's amazing.
That's not an easy thing to do.
(Amazed by his idol who never stops learning)
What made him cook in the first place?
When I used to draw manga,
I always ate boxed meals by myself.
It wasn't good for my health. So I've been cooking these days.
- You can communicate with him. - Right.
- Yes. - Only about simple things.
- But still. - But still.
Kian84's Japanese improved a lot.
His vocabulary is beyond the beginner level now.
- Right. - Yes.
I practiced that one, though.
- But still. - I practiced it.
Even if you practiced...
Right. Six months ago, you only knew the word for monkey.
(His Japanese improved a lot within 6 months.)
- Right. - Yes.
How is your health?
- I have pain all over my body. - He has pain all over his body.
My knees hurt.
- Your knees? - And my elbows too.
His knees and elbows hurt.
- My back also hurts. - And his back.
His back hurts too?
(Worried)
A few years ago, I got a herniated disc.
My spine is crooked.
- That must hurt. - So it hurts.
He had a herniated disc.
- Oh, no. - He had it.
- So he's not feeling well. - No.
It must be because he has a sedentary job.
Actually, sitting all the time takes a toll on manga artists' health.
I guess that's the case for all manga artists.
It's a tough job.
- It is? - We always have deadlines to meet.
He's just like you. He said it was a tough job.
The pressure of meeting deadlines was exhausting.
(He has the same difficulty as Kian84.)
- Does Kian84... - Yes?
still live alone?
- For now, yes. - For now?
I'm a bit lonely.
- You're lonely. - Right.
I'm sure he will make his future wife happy.
He can make tasty boxed meals like this one.
My goodness.
Gosh, what a sweet compliment.
He's so kind.
Thank you.
It feels great to see that he finished everything.
(He won't even leave behind a single rice grain.)
- How touching. - Gosh, he...
This was a lot of food, you know?
I made a lot of food on purpose.
And seeing him finish everything...
- He finished everything. - This was a lot of food.
It was delicious.
I cooked a bit more so as not to run out of food.
- But he finished everything. - Oh, my.
I'm so grateful.
(He finished the fried rice.)
- But he finished everything. - Oh, my.
(Choking up)
- This is the most touching moment. - Right?
- Seriously. I'm... - My gosh.
- I kind of felt bad too. - It didn't matter...
whether it tasted good or not.
I'm getting emotional right now.
I'm sure he was also...
- being considerate. - I think so too.
(After the meal, he gets started on his questions.)
He still has more questions.
(Chuckling)
Lately, I haven't seen...
your manga in Korea.
- I see. Is that so? - Yes.
- I... Right. - Are you working on a new series?
I'm curious about it too.
We haven't seen any new manga from him lately.
Well, I'm working on a new series now.
I finished up to Episode 3 out of 22 episodes.
Gosh, that's amazing.
I thought he was done with drawing manga.
Then do you...
still enjoy drawing manga?
I've been drawing manga on paper, the old-fashioned way,
after a long time.
- That's great. - The joy I used to feel...
back then is coming back to me.
(Pondering)
It's coming back.
In my opinion, being a manga artist...
is...
It's the most...
difficult.
- Difficult. - Difficult.
Is being a manga artist difficult for you as well?
The occupation suits me.
- It isn't easy to say that. - It's hard.
It really suits him.
Really?
He really seemed like a master.
He seemed like a proper manga artist.
He's incredible.
I wanted to be like him.
I wanted to draw comics like him.
(As he drew comics for many years,)
(he dreamed of how he'd be in the future every night.)
What I've drawn...
(I wanted to be like Ito Junji.)
(My idol seemed close, but also out of reach.)
I never reached that level.
I can only stare at it.
I've always thought that athletes...
such as soccer players and MMA fighters were very cool.
I realized that a manga artist could be even cooler.
(I realized that a manga artist could be even cooler.)
I was jealous too.
You're the same.
- Exactly. - That's right.
But I was looking at him as someone who never reached...
that level.
It felt a bit strange, to be honest.
You know,
everyone hits a roadblock in life.
But someone else might clear it for you.
Mr. Ito Junji might clear it for you through this opportunity.
I should keep my options open.
You might want to draw comics again.
- Exactly. - Of course.
(You could start anew today.)
(Glancing over)
- I have a favor to ask. - Okay.
Would you please give an autograph?
Of course.
- My goodness. - Really?
He'll give an autograph.
- An autograph. - Really?
I'll bring a pen.
- There's no need to hurry. - Wait.
- Hold on. - "Wait."
Why did he suddenly use a casual tone?
- "Wait." - You should've added "Please."
"Please wait."
- "Wait." - I was in a hurry.
(He gets a pen after being rude.)
It's the book I bought earlier.
(He hands over the book he bought ahead of time.)
Kian...
(Kian...)
(84)
(My goodness)
(Pulling down his glasses)
- He does it with so much care. - My goodness.
(He holds his breath while staring at Ito Junji's face.)
(Oh, my!)
He's drawing.
- What? - Did he draw?
- My goodness. - That's incredible.
- Seriously, that's incredible. - My goodness.
He's drawing.
(The master draws Tomie, his representative character.)
It's Tomie.
(My goodness)
I'm about to tear up.
He's drawing.
I became emotional then.
He wrote my name.
Then he lowered his glasses.
Throughout my life,
I've stared at that character hundreds of times.
He drew it right in front of my eyes.
I became emotional then.
I could see that he had done it all his life.
He's close to my mom's age.
He's in his mid-60s.
You know,
I could picture him drawing like that every day.
I could see how it ruined his discs.
Cartoon artists don't have personal lives.
They need to draw and focus on the stories.
They only sit at the desk in their studios.
I could picture it back then.
I was thankful that he was drawing for me.
(I was thankful.)
(He focuses until the end for Kian84.)
It's so touching.
I bet you felt like time had stopped.
I was a bit surprised.
My goodness.
(All done.)
That's incredible.
(My goodness)
Kian84.
Thank you.
(To Kian84)
(To repay him, he leaves a small message.)
- "Please stay healthy." - "Please stay healthy?"
I'm in tears.
(He can't take his eyes off the painting.)
(Taking out)
What is it?
No way!
Thank you.
This will be a family treasure.
What is it?
Those swirls are similar...
to what you made in your painting.
You should frame it.
I framed it.
- Really? - Yes, I framed it.
Please tell him that I'll pass it down to my son's son.
(Kangnam interprets with care until the very end.)
I'll give this to my daughter too.
To his daughter.
Mr. Ito Junji, please be healthy for a day...
"For a day?"
"Please be healthy for a day."
- You didn't mean that. - No.
- "Every day." - "Please be healthy every day."
You wanted to say "Day by day" or "Every day."
"Mr. Ito Junji, please be healthy for a day."
- "Enjoy today." - Seriously.
"Carpe diem."
- Every day, - Every day.
please be healthy.
(They take a photo together before they part ways.)
Here.
- You know, - In 1, 2, 3.
Kangnam looks very cool today.
I was so thankful for Kangnam.
You need to repay him.
I need to repay him.
Okay.
- Thank you. - He gave you a great memory.
Please come to Korea.
I'd love to meet again.
(Same here.)
(Inching closer)
(Let's shake hands.)
I realized later that my face was hot.
(It was a short, but dreamy moment.)
(Disappointed that it's over, he stares at the door.)
(My goodness)
I became emotional toward the end.
I guess that the fan's heart. Seriously, I felt it.
You couldn't meet his eye.
- Was it hard? - Yes.
I felt a bit awkward.
It didn't want to appear rude.
I wanted to show him my good side only...
because I was thankful for him. That was the thought.
You've done well enough.
You've done very well.
When he lowered his glasses for the autograph...
You became emotional.
He did that because he had...
- a bad eyesight. - Exactly.
- So I was thankful. - That's so touching.
Since he had brought this drawing, he didn't need to draw me anything.
But he drew this as well.
He drew it one more time.
- He drew with so much care. - You're right.
(To his gratitude, he gave him another drawing.)
I forgot to do something.
- What? - I wanted to explain...
my painting to him.
- Shall I call him back? - Don't be ridiculous.
But the idea of going, "This painting is such-and-such..."
- made me embarrassed. - Still...
So I didn't do that.
Mr. Ito Junji looked at you as if you were his junior.
- Right. - He seemed very proud.
- I had that thought. - What?
"Am I being flippant..."
"by starring in TV shows instead of drawing comics?"
(What?)
I suddenly had that thought.
It wouldn't be a bad idea to challenge yourself once more.
You have a lot of fans.
You've met a variety of people while starring in TV shows.
You went to the Arctic...
- and did many new things. - Yes.
If you draw comics again, something new will come out.
- That's right. - You're right. Someday...
I'll need to get hired to do that.
I can't do it just because I want to.
You'll get an opportunity if you want.
- By the way, thank you. - For what?
I felt grateful for you for the very first time.
He means it.
- Seriously. - Kangnam was very cool.
Since elementary school,
I enjoyed his works...
as I grew up.
I read his works even after I've aged.
Meeting someone like that...
felt like a dream.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm proud.
(He becomes emotional belatedly.)
Why are you crying now? You should've cried in front of him.
(Glancing over)
He has aged.
He was young.
Are there words you haven't said to Mr. Ito Junji?
I said,
"Please draw a lot of comics."
But I thought on my way back, "Isn't it my greed?"
To release new comics, he'll need to sit down for hours.
I loved starring in "I Live Alone" back in the day.
When I worked, I was just alone with my work...
in front of my computer.
So it was fun to meet new people here...
on "I Live Alone."
So I think it'll be great for him to live the life...
that's fun for him.
It's just my thought.
- You're a true fan. - Yes.
Is there anyone you want to meet?
The person I really wanted to meet...
passed away.
- Who was it? Larry King? - He was Larry King.
He was a legendary host...
of a talk show in the US.
He was my dream ever since I was little.
(The emperor of talk shows)
I nurtured my dream as I watched him.
He was my idol.
- I met my idol already. - Who was it?
TVXQ.
It makes sense.
- They debuted when you were young. - Seriously...
- You met them in your agency. - You realized your dream.
Yes. When I saw them for the first time,
I became emotional.
"I realized my dream."
"I've lived diligently."
It still feels like a dream.
- I get it. - It feels strange.
Things that never happen in real life...
come true.
Let's go.
(My goodness)
(He feels many emotions about the unreal interaction.)
I'll need to sleep over at your place.
Sleep over at my place.
It takes 30 minutes.
(After the dreamy meeting, he sets off to Kangnam's place.)
Who else do you want to meet?
Me?
- Mr. Ito Junji was... - Number one?
He was number one.
That's incredible.
Since I've grown old,
I didn't think that I'd have a fanboy moment.
- But I did. - Of course.
Everything I witnessed...
made me...
so nervous.
- Your face turned red. - Yes.
Mr. Ito Junji is on another level.
I felt close to him for some reason.
- This is Tokyo Station. - It's cool.
- It suddenly became quiet, right? - You're right.
(They pass the city center and move to the outskirts.)
So this is your place.
- Your neighborhood. - My neighborhood.
Your smell.
(Your neighborhood, your smell)
He's drunk on sentimentality.
- You had fuzzy feelings. - Exactly.
- I had fuzzy feelings. - Fuzzy feelings.
(With fuzzy feelings, he arrives at Kangnam's place.)
Does he still live in that apartment?
The place you've been to.
- Does he still live there? - Yes.
Excuse me.
All right.
(My goodness)
- Your place is nice. - Is it nice?
(An apartment with old vibes)
It's exactly the same.
You're right.
- Only my face is different. - It's the same except for one.
Only my face is different.
The display cabinet is the same.
He has lived there for about 40 years.
(The romantic memories are scattered around the house.)
(Merry Christmas)
It feels...
(Amazed)
I told you about it earlier. What was it called?
- Ferris wheel. - Okay.
- You can see it. - Let me see it.
- You can see the Ferris wheel. - You're right.
They're having fireworks!
Perfect timing.
- Is that Disneyland? - That's Disneyland.
(They see the fireworks from the theme park near the house.)
Do they have fireworks every day?
They have fireworks every day at this hour. Isn't it nice?
Yes.
(Looking at the fireworks reminds him of someone.)
(Meeting with his idol was as intense as fireworks.)
(He stares at the fireworks quietly as he thinks about the moment.)
It's nice.
(They wake up from the dream and come back inside.)
It's a nice house.
- It's warm inside, right? - Yes.
It's nice.
(Let's see.)
Did your father bring these liquors?
- My dad can't drink. - Okay.
So he collected liquors instead.
This liquor was made in Seoul in 1988.
Gosh, for the Summer Games at Seoul.
- There were many cool liquors. - Is it...
- from 1988? - Yes.
Is it Coke?
- It's from 1981. - Coke from 1981.
There are many precious items.
That's from 1984. Golf.
He likes baseball and golf.
(The collection has liquors from each era.)
Do you want to see my room?
It's to the left.
I grew up here...
- since the age of three. - Since you were a baby.
Yes. I used this room since the age of three.
(The room holds traces of him from his childhood to now.)
This is your room.
It's from the time Mom hit the door with a frying pan.
- Here. - Why did she do that?
She was angry. She wanted me to open the door.
Did you lock yourself inside?
- My mom was angry, - Okay.
- so I shut the door. - You did that.
So she hit the door with a frying pan.
- Let's say her son ran away. - Okay.
- And he locked the door. - Okay.
My mom could create...
a situation in which her son had to open the door.
What did she do? Can you guess?
What? What did she do?
My mom could create...
a situation in which her son had to open the door.
- What did she do? - What? What did she do?
Look at the structure.
- What? - What?
- What did she do? - What did she do?
- The room is below the hole. - Right.
What do you think will happen if she keeps adding water?
- It'll get flooded. - Gosh.
- Did she pour water? - She poured water...
- until I opened the door. - Really?
When the room got flooded, I had to open the door.
Just what did you do?
I don't remember. But my mom was very angry.
- I guess it was something big. - Right.
Didn't you see it?
There's a dented frying pan.
It got dented when she hit Kangnam with it.
- He showed me that. - Kangnam really is a strong man.
- Is that why he's called Kangnam? - It stands for "A strong man."
- She raised him as a strong man. - Really?
It was dented like this.
My mom is a genius.
(Laughing)
Thank goodness the wood didn't go bad.
They had to replace the wood.
(They had to replace the wood.)
(Kangnam begins to prepare dinner.)
(Meanwhile, Kian84 takes off the jacket.)
(He goes to the sink.)
(He washes the empty container that held lunch for his idol.)
Mr. Ito Junji...
- ate everything. - He ate everything.
I'm so touched.
- Did he eat all the food? - He didn't leave anything.
(He reminisces upon what happened as he looks at the container.)
(Kangnam begins to cook in earnest.)
It doesn't look half bad.
(Kangnam's sukiyaki is ready in no time.)
- It looks tasty. - It looks so delicious.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you for your hard work. - Well done.
(Thank you for your hard work.)
(Drinking)
(My goodness)
(Gosh)
Try it. Try the meat first.
- Thank you for the food. - Okay.
In Japan, they serve sukiyaki to an important guest.
I see.
Dip it... Dip it in the egg mixture.
I did that.
(Let me try it as well.)
- Hey, you didn't add any water. - No.
But it isn't salty.
(The taste makes him nod.)
Of course, it's delicious.
- It's good, right? - It's good.
- Not bad, right? - It's good.
(He picks up some konjac jelly noodles.)
Konjac jelly noodles taste really good to me.
The konjac jelly was good. It tasted good like that.
- Right - Drenched in the sauce.
- There's a lot of tofu. - Right.
(It's his first proper meal in Japan.)
(Kangnam shoves down the plain rice.)
This is the happiest moment.
(This is the happiest moment.)
(He takes a big bite of happiness.)
It feels like I owe you one.
Why think that way?
I'll grant you a wish of whatever you want.
- Really? - Yes.
It's a really hard thing to be able to meet Mr. Ito Junji.
You made it happen.
Don't mention it.
He seemed to respect you.
Why would he respect me?
He checked your work after I contacted him.
He agreed to meet you after that.
(Really?)
That's a great honor.
It felt like meeting a superstar.
He was small in size,
but he seemed really big to me.
It was my first time meeting an artist as well.
I had no chance to meet an animation artist.
- As he works in a different field. - Right.
It was great as he was very pleasant with us.
- Right. - Right.
I wonder if he will want to see me in Korea next time.
I talked with him a bit...
- when you were away. - Right.
I think he has plans to visit Korea with his family.
- In case he really comes, - Right.
- I should work on my Japanese. - Right.
I feel like I'm gaining momentum.
- Is that so? - Right.
I enjoy it.
I enjoy it like the first time...
- I started running last year. - Right.
Studying is fun.
I never thought studying was something fun in my life.
It never happened before?
Studying was something I've always hated.
But this is fun for some reason.
- Gosh. - It's weird.
It must feel fun as you have purpose behind it.
- Right. - This will make things faster.
- It's fun. - There will be even more momentum.
- Right. - It isn't fun if it's forced.
How was today?
Today,
thanks to Mr. Ito Junji,
- Gosh. - You know how to say "thanks to?"
You know how to say "thanks to?"
- Of course. - Look at you.
Gosh, Kian84!
That's a difficult term.
Right. Not a lot of people know that one.
- Beginners don't know that one. - Right.
Thanks to Mr. Ito Junji,
I studied Japanese...
for the first time.
And...
thanks to you,
it feels like...
I found...
a new life.
Your Japanese is good all of a sudden with some alcohol.
- That's natural. - Right.
- That happens naturally. - It pops out.
It's your doubt inside you that always stops you.
- Right. - There's no shame.
- It just comes out boldly. - Right.
So...
toward you, I really...
- and seriously... - He's saying it boldly.
feel thankful.
I have that heart toward you.
When you read Ito Junji's comics,
there's a certain feeling.
There are scary ones, but there are ones...
that make you feel like...
you've had a strange dream.
It felt like I was part of one of his comics today.
Unimaginable things happened.
(The idol he has always dreamed of)
(Spending time with Mr. Ito Junji)
(It was a thrilling day he will never forget about.)
It feels like...
I'm in a strange dream.
To me, he is like the universe.
(Finally Encountering My Universe)
Impressive.
The first guest of the Running Horses Special.
Bae Na Ra is here. Welcome!
- Hello. - Born in the Year of the Horse.
What was the response after being on the show?
Many people contacted me saying they enjoyed my episode.
(His day was full of consistent routines.)
(With his own rhythm,)
(the Routine Man lives each day.)
("I love his life with routine filled with neatness.")
("His life is so productive.")
And I used the skating board.
(Sliding)
Many people said they bought it as well.
Really?
Through a DM on social media,
there was an owner who wanted to stop selling them...
- as business was bad. - Gosh!
The owner thanked me for helping out.
The Running Horses Special is feeling great.
I'm curious about what kind of day you've spent this time.
- Let's take a look. - Right.
(Na Ra's World)
(He's sleeping with his blanket over his face.)
(Struggling)
(Tossing and turning)
(He finally shows his face.)
Wait. He's not at home.
- It's a tent. - It's a tent.
(He wakes up in a tent.)
It's still cold outside.
I cover my eyes and ears.
Right. He slept with a sleep mask.
Right. He covered his whole face.
It makes me feel like I'm in the same place...
no matter where I am.
Do you feel the same way in there as well?
Gosh, it's hot.
The tent looks really nice.
The tent is really big.
He knows how to enjoy a camping trip.
- There's a heater. - Right.
It has been a week since my musical was over.
To reward myself for working hard,
I came on a camping trip.
I came yesterday. It's my second day here.
It feels like he was there for... Oh, it's his second day.
(The wild traces of yesterday)
I went there for 3 days and 2 nights.
You go camping for up to 3 days and 2 nights?
Yes. As the size of the tent is quite big,
installing the tent...
and bringing it back down the next day...
- That makes sense. - feels too tiring.
How did you install a tent that big on your own?
How did he do that on his own?
- Did you do it on your own? - Is it a one-touch tent?
It's an air tent.
All you need to do is pump in air.
- What? - It's very...
- No need to put up tent poles? - No.
I don't go camping because of that.
- That's amazing. - It's that simple.
- Right. - One time,
it took me four hours to put up a tent.
- Do you still go camping? - I don't.
Strangely enough, it started to get popular again.
I quit camping for good.
(Half-awake)
(Getting up)
(I should head outside.)
(Opening it widely)
That moment feels great, though.
(It's morning with the bright sunlight.)
(Letting out a breath)
- Is it a mountain? - Probably.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- Gosh, that's great. - It's not a mountain.
- Is it a beach? - It's a beach.
Right.
(A camping ground that welcomes you with the sound of waves)
It has been around four years since I started camping.
It's a secret place of my own.
- It's amazing. - It's great.
Right.
It's a tranquil place...
where you can enjoy nature.
It's an outdoor camping ground.
It's a privately-owned land.
There's a sign.
- There's a phone number on it. - Right.
After calling the number...
- You send the money. - Right.
It's like a secret restaurant.
(He enjoys the place full of natural vibes.)
Gosh, it's cold.
It's still cold outside.
(He quickly returns to his tent after enjoying the vibes.)
- It's really big. - It looks nice.
Right.
The charm of solo camping is setting up...
another house of yours with my own equipment.
(Na Ra's house)
It has been six years since I moved in.
To use the space efficiently,
I hung everything on the walls.
There's everything I need stuck together.
I wanted to have everything within my reach.
It feels like he moved out.
Right. It feels like he moved.
To the left, I placed my bed...
and a place where I can...
- keep my things. - It's just the same, isn't it?
(The bed is lined up with his things.)
On the other side,
I placed my camping boxes.
I placed things...
for the best flow of movement possible.
He set up the tent neatly, just like his house.
- Right. - That's his character.
Right. It requires a lot of work to set things up like that.
To keep the whole place warm,
I always install a circulator above the heater.
That's amazing.
- As the heat moves upward? - Right.
Without that, it will be warm only around the heater.
That is why I'm wearing a short-sleeved shirt.
There have been many who went camping,
but it was the first time seeing a circulator, wasn't it?
It was my first time seeing that in my whole life.
Gosh, he's a professional campist.
- They're called campers. - Right.
(Feeling bitter)
(Chuckling)
Next to it,
I always place the carbon monoxide detector.
- I was always worried about that. - It's...
- Right. - If the heater turns off...
or the oxygen concentration drops down,
the alarm goes off right away.
It's a really important item.
You must have that with you.
- I see. - Right. No matter what.
That is why campers burn firewood...
with the stovepipes outside. In case of danger.
- Right. - Right.
It's outside the tent.
Do you not feel embarrassed when you say those things?
I feel really embarrassed.
- Right. - I've tried using...
Sook's seasonal tent before.
It was set up like that.
(The camper who knows a lot with his head)
(Na Ra was feeling drowsy on the bed.)
All right.
(He opens his camping box after a short break.)
Okay.
(He takes out cooking utensils without hesitation.)
(He wears cooking gloves for hygiene.)
(Peeking)
I should place this there.
You have to be diligent to do all of that.
Definitely.
(Na Ra gets out an onion first.)
He brought onions that weren't peeled.
Right.
(Cutting)
(He peels the onion above a basket.)
(It's placed there?)
I always neatly place a trash can.
I separated the bags for general waste...
and recyclables.
That way, it's easy to organize the trash.
So that was a trash can.
So they're separated.
Right.
There's a clip that can be used to separate the bags.
Usually, people use ramyeon boxes...
- Right. - to keep the trash.
- Right. - Right.
- We won't be able to do that. - We won't be able to do that.
We would always forget a thing or two.
- The carbon monoxide detector? - Right.
I would've forgotten about that 100 percent.
Right. The most important thing.
He's an extreme planner.
(The planner camper does everything according to plan.)
He's so meticulous.
Okay.
(Slicing)
(He chops down without hesitation.)
(The onion was diced easily.)
Onion.
(He slices the mushrooms into the pot freely as well.)
(He prepares the ingredients without hesitation.)
(Skilled)
Today's breakfast...
is something I always make when I go camping.
(The dish he makes often during a camping trip)
Doenjang jjigae with brisket.
- Doenjang jjigae with brisket. - Doenjang jjigae with brisket.
On a camping trip, most people grill meat...
and have ramyeon.
- Right. It's usually like that. - Right.
But expert campers...
(But expert campers...)
don't grill meat often.
I tend to make my own dish.
You grilled meat, didn't you?
What?
It's played right away.
(The wannabe camper's camping is...)
Are you serious?
Are you making kimchi?
- What are you saying? - That much salt is sprinkled?
It's lamb.
But to be honest,
it's more surprising that you made that on a camping trip.
Right. It's like fine dining.
Can you tell me why you don't grill meat or make ramyeon?
Is it because it's too simple?
As I go camping often, making the same things...
- You must be sick of them. - felt boring.
- You've experienced it all. - Right.
Expert campers will tell,
but my camping trip is cost-effective.
Everything isn't top-quality.
- But I have all that I need. - Right.
(Turning on)
(Na Ra's cost-effective camping trip even has a fire ready.)
- It's a store-bought sauce. - I always use those.
Bringing the doenjang separately...
- is too much work. - Right.
- I try to... - That's very reasonable.
do everything reasonably.
(The man who is perfectly prepared even with efficiency)
It tastes great when it's thick.
Right.
(As the doenjang jjigae boils...)
(Walking)
- What is that? - It must be a speaker.
- A Bluetooth speaker? - Yes.
He has everything.
(Rummaging)
(Dropping down)
(He takes out a white bag.)
- What is that? - A toothbrush?
What is that?
It's a shower wipe.
- Is it a large wet wipe? - A shower wipe?
A shower wipe.
Those are used even after a run.
I'm out in the wild.
When there are no shower facilities,
I bring and use them when needed.
- Right. - Right.
- I can wipe my whole body with it. - Right. I like that.
(He gently throws it away after using it.)
(He grabs the next item without hesitation.)
A shaver.
(The routines he followed at home)
(He does all of them even at the camping ground.)
He does the same things he did at home.
He's at a camping ground, but it feels like he's at home.
- Right. - Right?
(He diligently gets everything done as if he's at home.)
It's like he moved.
- Right. - Right.
Don't you feel bored when you go camping alone?
Enjoying that boredom...
- is part of camping. - Right.
That sense of solitude is enjoyed.
That's really hard to do.
What do you do when you go camping alone?
I spend a lot of time...
using all of those tools.
I think you'll be quite busy in there.
Setting things up...
- and taking a break is everything. - Right.
This is fascinating.
It didn't seem that interesting when Hyun Moo went camping.
I thought he was up to something strange on his own.
But watching this makes me want to go.
I would've been scolded if I were the one to do all of those things.
(The true charm of camping was felt after a while.)
(The Routine Man starts moving again.)
My gosh.
That looks delicious.
(Rummaging)
Right. This must go in now.
Gosh.
(The brisket with great colors goes in as a whole.)
Freshwater snails.
(Freshwater snails and tofu are added as well.)
- It's really simple. - Right.
All you need to do is throw everything in and boil.
Right.
(He picks up something that was near him.)
- What is that? - The air gun?
(He kept everything clean with the squeegee at home.)
Everything was neat at his house.
There are air guns used for cars.
- Right. I have that at home. - The one used to blow away snow.
- Right. - Right.
It was to blow away the sand.
(Picking up)
What?
A cucumber?
(Is he preparing another dish?)
What is that?
It was a salad sauce.
I made a simple cucumber salad.
(Eating)
(It tastes good as well.)
(The boiled doenjang jjigae is brought up.)
He does everything so naturally.
- It's done so smoothly. - Right.
(Focused)
The cooking torch?
(He even uses a cooking torch.)
(Picking up)
Why does the spice container look like that?
I made that spice container myself.
I went to a variety store.
And I bought several four-can containers,
and joined them together.
- You take them out when needed. - Right.
- Like this. - That's what I do.
That must be convenient.
How many kinds are there?
I have all sorts of things. Things like cumin,
shichimi, and bonito flakes.
(I have all sorts of things.)
Maldon Salt.
- Maldon Salt? - Right.
It's for the meat.
- I also have herb salt. - Herb salt?
- He has three types of salt. - As a seasoning.
(The first can of the spice container)
(Salt for grilled meat)
(He also sprinkles the pepper from the second can.)
They're all connected.
- They must be made that way. - Right.
I get excited on my own while getting things prepared.
- I imagine it in my head. - The things you like.
(He gets a generous amount of his favorite dish.)
(One more time)
(I must take a picture of this.)
(His meal looks flawless.)
(A perfect meal with the brisket)
Oyster bossam is a common dish when I go camping.
When there are leftover oysters,
I make oyster jeon with eggs.
That's the best thing to make.
And I also make spicy fishcake soup and kalguksu.
- I made gambas al ajillo as well. - He made everything possible.
I'm learning how to cook these days. We should go together some time.
- You are always welcome. - I'm learning how to cook.
I would love that.
I learn how to make around two dishes each time.
- At a cooking school? - Yes.
- You go to a cooking school? - You go to a cooking school?
Yes. A cooking school.
- That's fascinating. - As I've never tried cooking,
- I have no basic knowledge at all. - Gosh. You're committed.
As if it's personal training at a gym, I'm working hard to learn.
- That's a good idea. - Personal cooking.
Thank you for the meal.
All right.
(He slurps the soup first.)
That looks really good.
Gosh, this is great!
(Satisfied)
- That's all you need. - Right.
It tastes better when it gets boiled even more.
- Right. - Right.
All jjigaes taste better the second time.
- The 2nd and 3rd time. - Right.
(It tastes good from the first bite.)
(Sizzling)
(Having a piece of well-grilled meat as well)
It's way better.
(This time, he mixes rice with the stew.)
- Gosh, that's... - Gosh, while looking at the sea...
Doenjang jjigae and rice. That's the best.
(Having a bite of the cucumber salad)
(Glancing)
(He looks outside while eating.)
I try to enjoy nature as much as possible.
When I look outside,
I can hear the sea, birds, and wind.
Then I feel like I'm in nature.
(He enjoyed the morning with nature.)
(Nature-friendly dishwashing)
What do you think about when you eat alone?
Nothing comes to mind, really.
It's just nice.
I don't think about what to do next.
"I should do something."
- I don't worry about that. - You're not pressed.
- Right. I'm not pressed. - You go there to empty your mind.
That's right.
(While leisurely gazing at the sea,)
(he relaxedly wraps up the morning.)
Gosh, I'm so full.
(Putting it on)
(Na Ra heads somewhere after getting changed.)
There's a convenience store nearby.
- It's great. - Yes. There's a burger place too.
- There's a burger place too. - Fresh raw fish.
- That sounds good. - There's a raw fish restaurant too.
Yes.
Okay.
- Oh, he's running? - Right after eating?
- That's a mountain. - I'm running lightly.
(He starts running uphill.)
Gosh, it's uphill.
It's uphill.
It's great. It's even better.
(Na Ra ran whenever he had a chance.)
(He runs a lap even when he's camping.)
(Amazed)
Gosh, it's so nice.
Gosh, this place is pretty.
- Gosh, what is that? - His routine is the same as yours.
That's right. He enjoys a fun run.
- He likes running and camping. - That's right.
(Enjoying a happy run today as well)
Look at that. He's stopping.
I always do healthy running.
- Fun running? - You do fun running.
- He does fun running. - Come here.
- He does fun running. - There you go.
I was being careful not to touch your hand.
You still haven't given up on fun running.
I saw a marathon recently, and there were a lot of people.
There were a lot.
I think I still need to work on it more.
Why would you decide that based on the atmosphere?
It's gotten warmer, so more people are running.
- It's about time you step up. - I tried killing the trend,
but it keeps coming back.
There are too many people.
Well...
What?
What is it?
There's nothing much.
He must be looking for something.
Hello, ma'am.
I have something to ask.
Do you sell webfoot octopus?
Oh, webfoot octopus?
I ran today as well.
I saw a map,
and there was a port nearby.
Webfoot octopus is in season in March.
If you get a webfoot octopus full of roe...
and wrap it in a foil,
then put it on a charcoal grill with mayonnaise on,
it'll be incredibly savory.
I imagined that...
as I ran to the restaurant.
- It's the best in March and April. - It's really savory.
- Yes. - Do you sell webfoot octopus?
Do you sell webfoot octopus?
(Webfoot octopus at its peak season)
(The flesh is plump and chewy.)
(Do you have webfoot octopus that I love?)
- We don't have it yet. - You don't sell it?
You don't sell it?
- This is... - It is in season,
but I bet they don't sell it yet.
You don't have it yet? When do you sell it?
The boat has to go out to catch it.
- The boat has to go out? - It's still cold, so...
If you want to buy seafood,
you need to go to Oepori Seafood Market.
- What? - You need to cross the bridge.
It's a 15-minute drive, right?
- Yes. - By car, right?
(I see.)
All right. Thank you.
Then you need to run again.
If it's a 15-minute drive, fun runners don't run.
Exactly.
They don't have it either.
(He goes straight to the raw fish restaurant next to it.)
Hello, ma'am.
What kind of seafood do you sell?
We have sea bass, rockfish,
- Sea bass... - and flatfish.
- Sea bass, rockfish, and flatfish? - Yes.
Try going to Oepori Seafood Market.
- Oepori? - If you go there...
- You should go there. - Everyone told me...
- to go to Oepori Seafood Market. - Oh, really?
All right. Thank you!
Oepori?
Hold on.
(That wasn't my plan.)
It's a big market, so I need to go to another island.
(He thinks for a second as he has to go to another island.)
You can't.
It looks like he must eat webfoot octopus.
- That's the thing about planners. - That's right.
That's the problem of Type J.
- You can have rockfish instead. - I'd change my plan right away.
If that's the case, I wouldn't go camping.
That's right.
If I crave webfoot octopus that much, I'd take a taxi...
to Oepori Seafood Market and eat it there.
- When you're camping? - Of course.
- You'd eat at the restaurant? - What's wrong with that?
As long as you have a webfoot octopus.
"What's wrong with that?"
No, then you'd ruin it.
If you eat at a restaurant,
- my plan for camping disappears. - Exactly.
- That's right. - There's no point of camping.
Like I said, I'd eat webfoot octopus at the market.
- Yes, that's the strange part. - How is it strange?
You are camping with the tent set up,
and you eat at a restaurant. Isn't that strange?
Isn't it fun?
You have to eat the roe.
Then...
Gosh, I should try going elsewhere.
(Searching for a seafood market nearby)
I'm trying to look up...
a nearby port.
What is Eoryujeong Port?
What kind of place is Eoryujeong Port?
Eoryujeong Port is a small port...
on Seokmo Island, one of the islands in Ganghwa Island.
You can buy seafood at Eoryujeong Port.
Especially...
You can buy seafood at Eoryujeong Port. Especially...
He's running.
(He stops the AI from talking and rushes there.)
- He's running there? - He's going there?
- Was it nearby? - It must've been nearby.
All right.
- It's 2.4km. - It's 2.4km?
- Running 2.4km isn't bad. - But it's uphill.
(Exhaling)
(Lightly running with joy)
Since I'm a runner...
That isn't a fun run.
He runs the slope like that? Goodness.
I'm coming.
(Let's run toward webfoot octopus that's in season.)
The webfoot octopus you eat after running like that...
- is even more delicious. - That's right.
It doesn't taste the same if you go to a restaurant in a taxi.
You need to eat it after some effort.
- I think I'd lose my appetite. - You need to run.
Why would you lose your appetite?
It's the best after a taxi ride.
(He runs so that he can enjoy webfoot octopus even more.)
Wait a minute. I have to go down again?
Gosh, this isn't easy.
(The way to see webfoot octopus isn't easy.)
All right. Let's run.
Great. It's even better.
It's even better.
His legs are long, so he's fast.
Of course, he's fast.
Is it here?
(To be continued)
No way.
- For real? - Did you go to the wrong place?
(Na Ra kept running to eat webfoot octopus.)
Is it here?
No way.
- For real? - Did you go to the wrong place?
- Are you serious? - What is it?
- What is that? - What?
- You need to go there? - Oh, you have to cross that?
(It's a mountain trail!)
How does the GPS guide you...
- to a mountain trail? - Exactly.
The map showed a strange path.
- Serves you right. - It didn't show a proper road.
"Serves you right?"
You didn't listen to me and didn't get on a taxi.
You're so childish.
(Super childish)
Is this the right way?
I don't think I can do trail running.
Is this really right?
(He begins running, feeling confused.)
(The path is becoming rougher.)
I just thought...
that it was a shortcut and kept running.
(He's only run for 600m so far.)
(A challenging journey toward webfoot octopus)
- Of course it's tiring. - It annoys you if you run...
in that padded jacket because it's hot.
That's right.
You stink of sweat, and it annoys you.
It's tiring.
Gosh, I'm tired.
I'm so tired.
It's tiring.
(This won't do. Let me take a break.)
It's so tiring.
Gosh, this is...
(Taking it off)
This never occurred to me.
(Let's run again.)
(On a long quest to find webfoot octopus...)
(that was part of his plan)
(Getting more and more out of breath)
(Am I there yet?)
I became lighter after taking off the padded jacket.
- That's right. - Right. And it's cooler.
- It's cooler. - Yes.
(He ran the mountain trail while panting.)
All right.
(Barking)
I'll leave.
Goodness.
What is that?
(Both the dog and birds root for Na Ra.)
Maintain a slow pace.
(Fueled by everyone's support)
All right. I'm almost there.
(He's almost done with the webfoot octopus march.)
I'm finally here.
(He ran 2.4km to meet...)
It's huge.
This place is nice.
It's here.
It was a little bigger than the other port.
(Entering right away to look for webfoot octopus)
- Hello, ma'am. - Hello.
Are these all the seafood you have?
Yes.
Abalone, sea cucumber,
sea squirt, oyster, clams...
It looks like they don't have webfoot octopus.
I guess webfoot octopus isn't available yet.
I guess they really don't have it.
It's not available yet?
It's available a little later than other places.
It's available in May.
Oh, really?
(He overcame many obstacles...)
(to find webfoot octopus only.)
(He even came to the next village.)
(They don't have it either?)
What's the most delicious seafood among these?
We haven't started fishing operations yet.
Is that so?
Thank you. Have a good day.
(What do I do now?)
- He's running again? - He'll get a taxi in the end.
(Webfoot octopus, where on earth are you?)
(He found a direct seafood market.)
- Oh, a direct market. - I see.
- They must have it. - They must have it.
(Please)
No way.
(Clattering)
(It's closed.)
They must open only on weekends.
(Am I really not going to eat webfoot octopus?)
He must be frustrated.
I thought they'd have it for sure.
They said it wasn't the season to have webfoot octopus...
on Ganghwa Island yet.
So different regions have different seasons.
With that in mind,
I thought I should quickly come up with the next plan.
What do I do?
(Mental freeze)
- What do I do? - I had a mental breakdown then.
My plans for the day started falling apart.
Do you get stressed, then?
- That gives me stress. - Poor Type Js.
Hold on. A seafood market...
A seafood market in Oepo Port...
A direct seafood market? It's 7km away?
Gosh, seriously...
(I've already run 3.5km.)
That's too far to go all of a sudden.
Yes, he still has things to do when he gets back.
Right.
(Sighing)
(With just webfoot octopus on mind,)
(he continued to run.)
(Bitter)
I contemplated a lot.
(There's no webfoot octopus for me in this vast sea.)
That was totally meaningless.
It's just meaningless.
- We have a title. - Right.
(Title: "Meaningless")
(It's a bummer, but it can't be helped.)
(Acting fine)
(Clearing his throat)
Ma'am!
- Well, I... - What?
I wanted to cheer up.
- Is that so? - Yes.
I'll get some clams. What do you think?
We have scallops...
- They have many shellfish. - It's a spawning season.
Yes. I'll take 2kg.
- All right. - Okay.
Gosh, it looks delicious.
(His plan failed, but he replaced it with another seafood.)
I'll take 20 dollars' worth of abalone as well.
All right. I wish you good sales.
(He's done getting ingredients for dinner energetically.)
(Shall I go back now?)
Resuming your workouts.
(He begins running again with clams in his hands.)
With clams?
That's really tiring.
It's so heavy.
It was really heavy.
You're running with 2kg clams?
(Added weight that wasn't part of his plan)
Gosh, it's so cold!
(A back-and-forth running that wasn't part of his plan)
(He runs at full speed without giving up.)
Actually, it motivated me even more.
- "I'm going to do this." - I had to run perfectly...
- on the way back, - That's right.
so I'd think I had a good run.
- That's why... - That's right.
That'd complete your run.
(It's too early to get tired.)
I'm here!
(Keeping up with the pace until the end)
(Completed webfoot octopus run without webfoot octopus)
(Groaning)
(Trudging back to the tent)
I'm cold.
(Bitter)
That's when exhaustion hit me.
Let's take a nap.
(Sprawling out)
He should rest.
(Sighing)
(Goodness)
(Flapping)
The wind is strong.
(Whether it's windy or not,)
(he passed out gloriously after the webfoot octopus run.)
It must be tiring.
(The fate of Type J who went out, relying on his plan only)
That nap must feel really sweet.
(Soon, the sun starts to set.)
(Rustling)
(Getting up)
(He got up, shaking off the pain of a failed plan.)
Is it time for dinner?
Thirty minutes went by in the blink of an eye.
(He got up, shaking off the pain of a failed plan.)
(Pulling himself together)
He looks even more tired.
(Looking exhausted)
He looks so tired.
All right.
(Let's get back on track with the plan.)
(He recomposes himself...)
(and gets up.)
(He prepares dinner in earnest.)
(Moving the table outside first)
(He neatly sets up the lights too.)
(He follows through his plan without hesitating.)
(While he's busy getting ready for dinner...)
Bae Na Ra.
- Mr. Actor. - Bae Na Ra.
You scared me.
Hey!
- What are you preparing? - Come here.
- Come here. - Who are they?
Welcome.
- Thank you for coming all the way. - Not at all.
I invited my cherished friends.
They're my friends...
whom I've known for almost ten years.
One of them is Kim Do Hyun.
And the other one is Lim Jung Mo.
I've known them since my musical ensemble days.
That means you're really close.
I bought kimchi and meat.
(Laughing)
- I mean... - Gosh, I got food supplies.
You must've been excited because your friends came.
He became brighter.
They brought everything from meat to desserts.
- I was setting things up. - Can I get changed?
Yes, get changed in there.
(He changes into something comfortable right away.)
- Shall we grill meat right away? - Okay. Let's get started now.
Let's grill clams here.
- That... - Shall we grill meat there?
- You grill meat in a frying pan. - Okay.
Right? I'll grill scallops.
- Then... Wait. - Doesn't that sound good?
We have scissors and knives.
We see each other so often...
that we divide roles really fast.
- Everyone has their roles. - Yes.
Hey, suddenly...
- You feel energized? - Now that you're here,
I feel more confident all of a sudden.
(Webfoot octopus isn't available yet?)
- He must've been really hungry. - Friends are the best.
Actually, I...
went to buy webfoot octopus earlier...
because Incheon is famous for it.
But...
it wasn't available anywhere.
My neighborhood sells webfoot octopus.
This area doesn't sell it yet.
It looks so good, though.
(While sharing the plan that failed today...)
- It's the result of my hard work. - It's the result of your hard work?
(Dinner prep is almost done.)
(Exclaiming)
Great work.
- All right. - Let's eat.
- Go ahead and eat. - Let's eat.
(Doenjang jjigae with beef brisket...)
(and freshwater snail made in the morning)
Stew tastes better when it's reheated.
- I boiled it again. - Right.
(A meal of Na Ra's camping food is completed.)
It's to die for.
- Let's cheers before we drink. - Shall we?
(Shouting)
What is that?
- Their shouting is... - What? What was that about?
It's not ordinary.
We always do a cheer before we do our play.
We're used to it,
so we always shout like that when we gather.
- Even when you drink? - It's our basic way...
to boost our energy.
(Cheering with a solid shout)
(Boosting their energy)
- This is cooked. Try it. - Okay.
Try one each.
- Here. Eat your fill. - Nice.
(Shall we eat in earnest?)
Eat your fill.
(Exclaiming)
(Taking a bite of doenjang jjigae made with love)
I can clearly taste freshwater snail.
- Really? - It's good.
- Is it? - Yes.
- I'm glad. - It's delicious.
I'm glad.
(Now that you tasted the stew, try the meat.)
It's good, right?
(This is good too.)
It's good.
Try it.
This spot has a great view.
(Feeding 1 by 1)
He's like our mom.
- He's like a mother bird. - I know.
(Dinner is going smooth.)
(Glancing)
- Right. - And we wouldn't be able to do it.
- Right. - It wouldn't be fun.
(Pouring as is)
You should lift it like this.
- Of course. - That's great.
(They're used to it.)
This is the easiest and simplest way...
for me to cook deliciously when I go camping.
The stir-fried pork sauce.
(It's...)
It's the best.
If you get tired of having meat,
you can grill it with the sauce.
(You can apply the sauce and grill it.)
You can start eating again.
- Really? - Yes.
It must taste like charcoal-grilled gochujang pork belly...
from a really good restaurant.
- Exactly. - Right?
It's really good.
You must grill it with charcoal.
- With charcoal. - With charcoal?
- Guys, this is a game-changer. - All right.
It's like you're applying sauce on eel.
I'm sure you're going to enjoy this.
(Sniffing)
(This is it.)
- It looks so good. - That sauce is the kick.
- It looks nice. - What's that? Mushroom?
(What is that?)
- It's pork neck. - Oh, pork neck.
Yes.
You're eating so much meat.
(You're eating so much meat.)
- I know. - You said you wouldn't eat it.
(You said you wouldn't eat it.)
- Camping is all about ramyeon... - And meat?
and meat.
That's a classic combination.
- The basics are the best. - That's right.
There's a reason why everyone eats that.
- Of course. - Yes, you're right.
- Let's see. - It's all grilled, so try it.
Try it.
It's too hot!
It's...
Their actions are exaggerated because they're musical actors.
"It's too hot!"
He had a performance up until the day before.
(The next one trembles with fear.)
It's hot.
- It's hot. - Let it go.
(Let it go!)
(Even if it's hot, he slurps it up.)
(He tries a bite too.)
- Hey. - It's so good, right?
- It's good even if it's hot. - It's really good.
(Approving)
Shall I grill this for you?
How is it?
(He's indeed a planner. He prepared a gridiron.)
With the gridiron? Do you happen to have butter?
- I don't have butter. - Why not?
- It's somewhat... - You've become loose.
- What do you mean? - He used to have everything.
- I used to bring everything. - Because earlier...
There's a convenience store nearby.
(Right. There was one earlier.)
- He's right. - You're right.
It didn't occur to me.
- The convenience store? - The convenience store?
You can't deviate from your plans at all.
That's why I need to plan everything in advance.
- You should've thought of that too. - Right.
- I should've thought that far. - I mean...
You can't cope with unexpected situations at all.
- You only stick to your plans. - You only do what you planned.
- It's frustrating. - Right.
Didn't you mean you'd spread it and apply sauce on it?
- Yes, apply it. - Is he right?
Apply it to the front and back.
- That's it. - That's it.
- That's it. - You got it.
That's it. Great.
- Yes, that's what I wanted. - That looks delicious too.
- It is delicious. - All right.
I wonder how the sauce tastes.
- After that... Okay, stop. - Okay.
- This is it, right? - Awesome.
You'll grill it as is?
You're pressing it down with the gridiron.
It's looking fine.
Add a smoky aroma.
- This is it. - That's guaranteed to be delicious.
- I want to eat it again. - It looks delicious.
Shall we try it?
Try it. It must be really good, right?
(The mother bird feeds the babies first again.)
Thank you.
- Is it well-marinated? - It's good.
You can tell right away.
(Exclaiming)
It's hard not to be good.
(Squirming)
(Adding hot sauce this time)
Gosh, look at this. Hey, try this.
(Taking a big bite after applying lots of sauce)
- No, on this. - Hey.
That. Is it Tabasco sauce?
Gosh, Na Ra.
(This is it, guys.)
- I like that. - Is it good?
It's really good.
It tasted a bit like Southeast Asian food.
(It tasted like Southeast Asian food.)
(Do Hyun hurriedly tries a bite too.)
It's tasty. It's so good.
It's good, right?
- You need to eat spicy version too. - It's good, right?
- It's amazing. - Right?
The Tabasco sauce is delicious.
- It's good. - Right?
(The customer satisfaction of Na Ra's meal is excellent.)
The sun is setting.
- You go camping for that. - That's right.
- The sunset. - The glow of the setting sun.
It's to die for.
- The view is amazing. - It's the best.
- The view is beautiful, right? - Yes.
I've been to Kota Kinabalu a lot...
because I like sunsets.
- To see sunsets? - Yes.
Are sunsets in Kota Kinabalu different?
It's famous as one of the world's top three sunset spots.
I fell in love with the sunset there.
So I looked for beautiful sunset spots...
- in Korea as well. - Oh, beautiful sunsets.
- You must like sunsets. - Yes, I love sunsets.
The sunsets on Daebu Island, Jebu Island,
and Ganghwa Island are all beautiful.
- That's right. - They're beautiful.
The West Sea...
- has beautiful sunsets. - Right.
If you go to the Yeouido Park after it rains,
it's the best.
- The Yeouido Park? - The Yeouido Park?
- What? - The sky of Yeouido...
- with no dust... - No dust.
the day after it rains.
The sunset seen among the forest of buildings.
- That's right. - I wonder how it looks.
- Hey, let's take photos. - Sounds good.
(They gather around...)
(to leave a photo to remember today.)
- It turns out great when we gather. - Great.
- It turns out great, right? - Awesome.
The visuals are amazing.
I'm sorry, but...
Having self-esteem is really important to me.
I had a really low self-esteem when I was young.
Through the process of preparing camping in my way...
and organizing it,
I've become much more independent.
My self-esteem increased a lot too.
Self-esteem.
I try to take control of everything at a time like this.
In my own world and space.
- Great job today. - Great job.
I was happy thanks to you.
- Thanks, guys. - I'm grateful too.
This is fun.
(Next story)
(He gained attention...)
(for a touching mother-child story with Kim Hye Soo.)
(Even next to the great actors,)
(his presence stood out.)
(With remarkable performances across all genres,)
(the rising star won all sorts of awards...)
(from various network channels.)
Hello, I'm...
(It's been 13 years since he started living alone.)
(Actor Bae In Hyuk)
(Since he was young,)
(he was told he was mature.)
(Well-behaved...)
(and quiet)
(Tapping)
(Gosh, I'm hungry.)
(The microwave is way too slow!)
(I'm in a hurry, but I guess you're not.)
(Opening)
(Oh, no!)
(Well-behaved and quiet)
(Scrubbing)
(Washing his face vigorously too)
(Rolling)
(I guess it doesn't smell that good for you either.)
(In Hyuk is particularly well-behaved.)
(What shall I do now?)
(Shall I go out too?)
(Digging)
(Where are you?)
(I said, where are you?)
(The look in his eyes is different from that at home.)
(This one is no good.)
(Chuckling)
(That Man's Double Life)
(I must control myself.)
Gosh, don't get too excited.
(I see so many cute things here.)
(Hyun Moo is completely absorbed in shopping?)
(Today is...)
(Moo-KEA Day.)
(Moo-KEA's instincts were awakened...)
(by Hue's interior design philosophy.)
(Hue and interior design)
(Hue-terior)
(That's the vibe Moo-KEA is going after.)
(Hue's cup)
(Hue's vase)
(Hue's lamp)
(A simple and sophisticated style)
(That screams Hue.)
(Simple)
(Simplicity is the answer.)
(Hue)
Here comes the lunatic.
I'm a lunatic.
(I must keep it simple now.)
This is daunting.
(Screaming)
(Torturing himself with Hue-terior)
(Punching)
(That hurts.)
I should throw this out.
(It's not simple, is it?)
(Hue)
(Welcome to Moo-KEA)